Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Area
  - Films and Filming in NYU Area (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Filming of "Soup for One", 1981; wsa_2_5_31; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 5, Item 31)
    - Filming of "Four Friends", 1980; wsa_2_5_32; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 5, Item 32)
    - Film Being Projected, undated; wsa_2_5_33; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 5, Item 33)
  - Graffiti (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Graffito (Waverly): "Take Away Nancy's Little Gun and Give Her the Business End of It!", 1981; wsa_3_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Graffiti on Number Seven Subway, 1980; wsa_3_3_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Number Seven Subway - Car Interior, 1980; wsa_3_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Graffiti on Number Seven Subway, 1980; wsa_3_3_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Graffito in Stairwell, undated; wsa_3_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Graffiti, 1984; wsa_3_3_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Person Defacing Desk, undated; wsa_3_3_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Person Defacing Desk, wsa_3_3_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Graffito: "Join the Immoral Minority!", 1981; wsa_3_3_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Graffiti: "NYU Diploma Please Take One" (toilet paper), undated; wsa_3_3_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Graffiti: "NYU Diploma Please Take One" (toilet paper), undated; wsa_3_3_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - "Sit On It", undated; wsa_3_3_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 12)
    - Graffiti at Houston and Bowery Streets (Keith Haring), circa 1980 - 1989; wsa_3_3_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 13)
    - Graffiti at Houston and Bowery Streets (Keith Haring), circa 1980 - 1989; wsa_3_3_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 14)
    - "Freedom is Qualitative and Quantitative" (Main Building), undated; wsa_3_3_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 15)
    - "Smash the State. Anarchy. Smash Capital...", undated; wsa_3_3_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 183, Folder 3, Item 16)
  - Greene Street (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Corner of Greene Street and Washington Place, 1935; wsa_3_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Greene Street, 1964; wsa_3_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Greene Street Looking North From West 3rd Street, 1964; wsa_3_4_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Greene Street, 1964; wsa_3_4_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Greene and Waverly Streets Looking South, 1964; wsa_3_4_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Eighth Street and University Place, Looking East, undated; wsa_3_4_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Eighth Street Looking West From Greene Street, wsa_3_4_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - South Side of West 4th Street Looking West from Greene Street, undated; wsa_3_4_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - 262 Greene Street, 1969; wsa_3_4_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Greene Street, 1964; wsa_3_4_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Washington Place and Waverly Place, undated; wsa_3_4_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Greene Street at Wooster, undated; wsa_3_4_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - East Building, Washington Place and Greene Street, undated; wsa_3_4_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - Greene Street and Waverly, undated; wsa_3_4_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 14)
    - East Building, Washington Place and Greene, undated; wsa_3_4_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - North Side of West 3rd Street Looking East From Wooster Street, undated; wsa_3_4_16 (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - Workers, undated; wsa_3_4_17 (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - Udell Graphic Center, undated; wsa_3_4_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Tillis Luncheonette, 1965; wsa_3_4_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 19)
    - Street Corner, undated; wsa_3_4_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 20)
    - Beatty Hatters Printing, undated; wsa_3_4_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 4, Item 21)
  - Hebrew Union (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Hebrew Union College, undated; wsa_3_6_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Hebrew Union College, undated; wsa_3_6_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Ground-Breaking Ceremony at Hebrew Union College, undated; wsa_3_6_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Construction of Hebrew Studies Center, 1978; wsa_3_6_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - "House of Genius" (61 Washington Square South), 1948 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - South Side of Washington Square South Looking East from Thompson Street, 1948; wsa_3_7_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Genius Row, undated; wsa_3_7_02 (Box 177, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Jefferson Market 6th Avenue and 9th street) (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - Children Protesting Closing of Jefferson Market Library Closing, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - Jefferson Market, Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_8_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 5)
    - People Gathering Signatures Against the Closing of the Jefferson Market Library, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_3_8_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 6)
    - Jefferson Market Police Court (engraving), 1878; wsa_3_8_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 8, Item 7)
  - Map (circa 1820-30), 1820-1839 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Map of Greenwich Village (engraving), 1822; wsa_3_9_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - MacDougal Street (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - North Side of MacDougal Alley Looking East From MacDougal Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Washington Square South and MacDougal Street, 1962; wsa_3_10_02 (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - MacDougal Street and Washington Square South, undated; wsa_3_10_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 3)
    - West Side of Washington Square West Looking North from West 4th Street, 1947; wsa_3_10_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 4)
    - MacDougal Street, Between Minetta Lane and West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 5)
    - MacDougal Street South of West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 6)
    - North Side of West 3rd Street Looking East from Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_10_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 7)
    - East Side of MacDougal Street Looking South from West 8th Street, 1947; wsa_3_10_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 8)
    - North Side of West 3rd Street Looking West 8th from MacDougal Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 9)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street Looking North from Minetta Lane, undated; wsa_3_10_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 10)
    - MacDougal and West 3rd Street Looking West on West 3rd Street, undated; wsa_3_10_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 11)
    - Calypso Club, MacDougal Street, undated; wsa_3_10_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 12)
    - South Side of West 4th Street Looking East from Sixth Avenue, undated; wsa_3_10_13 (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 13)
    - South Side of West 8th Street Looking West from MacDougal Street, undated; wsa_3_10_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 14)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street Looking South from West 8th Street, wsa_3_10_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 15)
    - East Side of Sixth Avenue looking south from West 4th Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 16)
    - East side of Sixth Avenue Looking North from West 3rd Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 17)
    - West side of MacDougal Street looking north from West 3rd Street, 1945; wsa_3_10_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 18)
    - East side of Sixth Avenue looking south from West 8th Street, circa 1947; wsa_3_10_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 19)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street Looking South from Minetta Place, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 20)
    - West side of MacDougal Street looking north from West 3rd Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 21)
    - Buildings 114-120 Along MacDougal Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 22)
    - Intersection of MacDougal Street and Washington Square South/West 4th Street, 1962; wsa_3_10_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 23)
    - West side of MacDougal Street looking south from West 4th Street, circa 1940's-1950's; wsa_3_10_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 24)
    - South side of West 4th Street Looking West from MacDougal, ca 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 25)
    - South side of MacDougal Alley, circa 1947; wsa_3_10_26; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 26)
    - MacDougal Street, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_27; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 26)
    - 118 MacDougal Street, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_28; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 28)
    - MacDougal Street - Square Tavern, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_29; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 29)
    - MacDougal Street - No. 138, Bat Restaurant, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_30; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 30)
    - MacDougal Street - No.138, Ground Floor Hallway, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_10_31; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 31)
    - Le Figaro Cafe, circa 1950s; wsa_3_10_32; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 32)
    - MacDougal Street - Washington Square Art Show, 1955; wsa_3_10_33; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 32)
    - MacDougal Street - View of Calypso Club, circa 1950s; wsa_3_10_34; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 34)
    - MacDougal Street - Rear of No. 144, Interior Court, circa 1950s; wsa_3_10_35; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 35)
    - MacDougal Street - Caffe Reggio, circa 1980s-1990s; wsa_3_10_36; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 177, Folder 10, Item 36)
  - Mercer Street (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Mercer Street and Washington Place, 1956; wsa_3_11_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - Mercer Street Looking East, 1965; wsa_3_11_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - Looking South on Mercer Street, circa 1950s-1960s; wsa_3_11_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 4 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 3)
    - Corner of Mercer Street and Waverly Place, circa 1950s-1960s; wsa_3_11_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 4)
    - Mercer Street, 1964; wsa_3_11_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 5)
    - Mercer Street and Washington Place, 1964; wsa_3_11_06 (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 6)
    - Mercer Street - Hot Dog Vendor, 1981; wsa_3_11_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 7)
    - Mercer Street and Washington Place, 1964; wsa_3_11_08 (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 8)
  - Parsons School of Design/New School (Box 178)
    - Parsons School of Design, circa 1960s-1970s; wsa_3_12_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 2 ½ inches (Box 177, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - Parsons School of Design, circa 1960s-1970s; wsa_3_12_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 4 inches (Box 177, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - New Sailors' Snug Harbor Properties, 1947-1955 (Box 178)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, 1947; wsa_3_13_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Washington Mews No. 12 - South side, looking east, 1948; wsa_3_13_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Washington Mews No. 12, 1948; wsa_3_13_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Folder 3)
    - Washington Mews, No. 12, circa 1947; wsa_3_13_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 4)
    - Washington Mews No. 12 - south side, looking east, circa 1947; wsa_3_13_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 5)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, circa 1946; wsa_3_13_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 6)
    - 262 Sailors Snug Harbor, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_13_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 7)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, Looking East, 1955; wsa_3_13_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 8)
  - Provincetown Playhouse, 1936 (Box 178)
    - Provincetown Playhouse, 133 MacDougal Street, 1936; wsa_3_14_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178)
  - 6th Avenue, 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Looking North at East Side of Sixth Avenue, From Washington Place Towards Waverly Place., Circa 1940-1949; wsa_3_15_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 1)
    - 6th Avenue "El" Turning West Into West 3rd and West Broadway, circa 1940-1949; wsa_3_15_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 3/4 x 6 5/8 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 2)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, from West 8th Street, 1945; wsa_3_15_03; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 3)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, From Washington Place, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_04; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 4)
    - Looking East from 6th Avenue at the North Side of Waverly Place, 1945; wsa_3_15_05; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 5)
    - West Side of 6th Avenue Between 3rd and 4th Streets, 1945; wsa_3_15_06; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 6)
    - Looking North at East Side of 6th Avenue, from West 4th Street, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_07; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 7)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street, looking South from Intersection of Washington Square South and Washington Square West, 1945; wsa_3_15_08; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 8)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, from Washington Place, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 9)
    - Looking North at East Side of 6th Avenue, towards 8th Street, 1945; wsa_3_15_10; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 10)
    - 6th Avenue, 1860 (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - 6th Avenue, 6th and 14th (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - Slum Clearance Project (Between West 3rd and Houston), 1950-1959 (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - 6th Avenue El turning west onto West 3rd Street, wsa_3_17_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 3/4 x 6 5/8 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 1)
    - Site of Loeb Student Center, demolition of old building, Washington Square South, November 12, 1957; wsa_3_17_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 2)
    - Demolition, Washington Square South, June 19, 1957; wsa_3_17_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 3)
    - Washington Square Project, Southeast Slum Area, West Houston between Wooster and West Broadway (north side)., 1955; wsa_3_17_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - Washington Square Project, Southeast Slum Area, North side of West 3rd Street between Wooster and W. Broadway., 1955; wsa_3_17_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 5)
  - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue's Cemetery (West 11th Street), 1970 (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 1)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 2)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 3)
  - Studio Building (51 West 10th), 1858 (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Studio Building, 51 West 10th Street, 1858; wsa_3_19_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Fires, NYU and area (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Fire Alarm at Rubin Residence Hall (exterior), 1981; wsa_3_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Firemen, undated; wsa_3_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Westside Pier, undated; wsa_3_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Firefighter at Work in Silhouette, undated; wsa_3_1_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Fire at Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_3_1_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Aftermath of Fire in Main Building, 1983; wsa_3_1_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Joseph G. Fitzgerald, Assistant Director and Manager Protection Department, 1981; wsa_3_1_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Joseph G. Fitzgerald, Assistant Director and Manager Protection Department, 1981; wsa_3_1_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books, undated; wsa_3_1_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 2 x 3 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Firefighters, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Silhouette of Fireman, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Firefighters, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Fireman, undated; wsa_3_1_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Fire on Sullivan Street, 1983; wsa_3_1_17; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Fire, Sixth Avenue, 1981; wsa_3_1_18; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Firefighters, undated; wsa_3_1_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Fire, Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_3_1_23 (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books (exterior), undated; wsa_3_1_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 24)
  - Grace Church (Box 179, Folder 2)